(Gablehouser:)Today's preliminary match
features two great teams:
(Gablehouser:)AA versus PMS.
(Howard:)All night long, y'all.
(Gablehouser:)Okay, well, let's jump right in.
First question.
For 10 points. "What is the isospin
singlet partner of the pi-zero meson?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
- PMS?
- The eta meson.
(Penny:)Correct.
- Formal protest.
- On what grounds?
(Sheldon:)The Velcro on my wrist brace
caught on my shirt.
Denied. All right, for 10 points.
"What is the lightest element on Earth
with no stable isotope?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
(Leonard:)- AA?
- And, of course, the answer is technetium.
(Gablehouser:)Terrific.
Next question. "What is the force
between two uncharged plates...
...due to quantum vacuum fluctuation?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
- PMS?
- And Sheldon can suck on...
(Raj:)- ...the Casimir effect.
GABLEHAUSER: Correct.